It's kind of stylish.
なんかオシャレだ
That's good.
それいいじゃん
It smells so bad.
ちょーにおい
What is this?
何これ?
Amazing here.
すげーここ
What is this? It's scary.
なにこれ、こわ
Super beautiful.
超きれい
It kind of fits there.
なんかそこに合ってるもん
ERROR
乗るとき気をつけないと、ごはんってしみる
I tried to sleep and fell on my side.
寝てみて横に転んどく
It looks like it's going to fall.
なんか落ちそうだね
Scary, scary.
こわい、こわい
Looks like Baratone is going to take off his clothes.
バラトーンの脱がしそうだね
amazing.
すごい
ERROR
ゆれる
I want this at home.
家に欲しいね、これね
Do you sleep there?
そこに寝る?
Yeah.
うん
delicious?
おいしい?
Yeah.
うん
What is that?
なにそれ?
Terramites.
テラミッツ
Mascarpone.
マスカルポーネ
Does it really suit you?
本当に合ってんの?
ERROR
マスカルポーネテラミッツ
That's right.
そう なんだよ
That seems sweet.
甘そうだね
Isn't it really sweet?
めちゃくちゃ甘いんじゃない?
No, it's bitter.
いや、苦い
Is it bitter?
苦いの?
It's so beautiful.
すげーきれいだね
The sky is of various colors.
いろんな色の空になってる
Are you eating pancakes?
パンケーキ食べんの?
eat.
食べる
Are you hungry?
おなかすいた?
Eat a lot.
いっぱい食いな
ERROR
ペンキに書いてあるやつ
Hey.
へー
ERROR
甘いもの大好きなの
I like paint.
ペンキが好きなの
ERROR
ペンキかわいいよ
I wanted to go to the aquarium today.
今日水族館行きたかったけどな
I wanted to go.
行きたかった
Then I better go paint.
そしたらペンキに行ったほうがいい
It looks delicious.
おいしそうに食べますね
I'm still coming.
まだ来ちゃう
How many points?
何点ですか?
100 points.
100点
100 points?
100点?
That's cool.
かっけー
Looks delicious.
おいしそう
It's my first time.
初 めてだ
Hello.
こんにちは
It's cute.
可愛いね
thank you.
ありがとう
The style is nice too.
スタイルもいいし
What do you usually play?
普段何して遊んでるの?
I went shopping.
買い物行ったり
I like shopping.
お買い物好きなんだ
I like it.
好きです
Are you going with friends?
友達と行くの?
I'm going with a friend.
友達と行きます
ERROR
すごいアイドルみたいだね
The face.
顔が
That's not true.
そんなことない
You'll be very popular, right?
モテるでしょ、すごく
I'm not popular at all.
全然モテないです
You're definitely making a fake face.
絶対嘘の顔してるな
How many people have experience?
経験人数は何人いるの?
About 5 people.
5人くらい
There are about 5 people.
5人くらいいるんだ
Did you call him handsome?
イケメンってやった?
I don't know.
わかんない
That's right.
そうなんだ
Do you like older people?
年上の人は好き?
I like it.
好きです
Today, I'm going to take a lot of naughty pictures,
今日さ、 いっぱいエチなとこ撮っちゃうけどさ、
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
You're doing it.
してるよね
How many centimeters tall?
身長何センチ?
It is 160 cm.
160センチです
There are quite a few.
結構あるんだね
Who are you going to tell me?
誰に言ってるって言われる?
Not much.
あんまり
Not told?
言われない?
I see.
そ っか
Well then, take a picture of that mask and show me your face.
じゃあさ、 そのマスク撮って、 ちょっと顔見せて
It's super clean and cute.
すごい清掃で可愛いね
Even her shy face is cute.
恥ずかしがってる顔も可愛いよ
What do you have the most fun doing?
何してるときが一番楽しい?
I like it when I watch movies.
映画見てるとき好きです
Watch a movie.
映画見るんだ
yes.
はい
What do you like?
何が好きなの?
I prefer that.
ほうがが好きです
It's Japanese.
日本のやつね
I don't see many overseas ones.
海外のやつあんま見ないんだ
Those who see will see.
見るやつは見ます
Those who see, see.
見るやつは見る
ERROR
なんかおっぱい大きくない?
How many cups are there?
何カップあるの?
I have an E cup.
Eカップある
That's amazing.
すごいね
I don't know if I'll take lots of pictures later.
あとでいっぱい撮っちゃわからない
It's a good idea.
はずいね
Please stand up for a moment.
ちょっとさ、 立ってみて
It looks a little big when you stand up.
立つとちょっと大きく見えるね
Her legs are also white.
足も真っ白
Are you trying not to get sunburned?
日焼けしないようにしてんの?
No, it doesn't burn much.
いや、あんまり焼けないです
It doesn't burn.
焼けないんだ
Looks like I'm not going to the beach or anything.
海とか遊び行かなそうだね
Have you ever been there?
行ったことある?
I've been there before.
行 ったことあるんだ
Looks like I'll be picked up soon.
すぐナンパされそう
No, I won't go in.
いや、入らないですけど
That's right.
そうなんだ
Look back.
後ろ向いてみて
ERROR
お尻も結構大きいね
Maybe so.
そうかもしれない
Try wrapping the skirt slightly.
軽くスカート巻いてみて
It's a very close line.
ギリギリのラインだね
Try raising it.
上げてみて
Your naughty panties are open.
エ ッ チなパンツ開いてるね
I like black.
黒好きなんだ
I like it.
好きなんだ
It has a whitish image, though.
白っぽいイメージあるけどね
The face.
顔が
Then, I'll just take off my jacket.
そしたらさ、 上着だけ脱いじゃおうか
I think white waisas looks good on you.
や っぱ白いワイサス似合うね
thank you.
ありがとう
Try pasting it on.
パツンと貼ってみて
My boobs are big.
おっぱい大きいよ
Kuro-chan, let's take this button off.
黒ちゃんさ、 これボタンちょっと取ろうか
If you look closely, you can see that her breasts are big.
近くで見ると、 お っぱ い大きいね
It's big, isn't it?
大きいよね
This one is thin though.
こっちは細いのに
Looks like it smells good.
いい匂いしそう
copper?
どう?
It smells like soap.
シャボンの匂いがする
Your skin looks amazing.
すげえ肌きれいだね
pure white.
真っ白
How does it feel to have your breasts touched?
おっぱい触られてどう?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'm getting nervous.
緊張しちゃうね
soft?
柔らかい?
It's so soft.
すごい柔らかい
So let's move it a little bit.
そしたらさ、 ちょっとずつずらしてみようか
Very beautiful breasts.
めっちゃきれいなおっぱい
Wow, the color is so pale.
すごい、色が薄い
So beautiful.
すごいきれい
It was seen.
見られちゃったね
Amazing boobs.
すごいな、おっぱい
It's so beautiful.
めちゃくちゃきれいだ
It doesn't seem like you've been rubbed much.
あんま揉まれたことなさそうだね
Breasts.
お っぱいね
Then sit on the bed.
そしたら今度さ、 ベッドに座って
bed?
ベッド?
It's not a bed, it's a sofa.
ベッドじゃねえや、ソファ
oh yeah.
そうそう
On top, sit in a sitting position.
上、体座にして
Would you like to open it?
それ開いてみ?
In an M-shape.
M字に
oh yeah.
そうそう
It's beautiful.
きれいだね
Yeah.
うん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
You've never been taken from something like this, right?
取られたことないでしょ、こういうの
do not have.
ない
I want them to open up more.
もっとガバって開いてもらう
Try making your pants slimmer yourself.
自分でさ、 パンツ細くしてみて
Tightly on top.
上にぎゅっと
Tight like this.
こうやってぎゅっと
I can barely see it.
ギリギリ見えない
Wow, that's so naughty.
うわー、すっごいやらしいね
I could see it a little.
ちょっと見えちゃったって
Yeah.
うん
Did you take Kuro-chan's clothes off?
黒ちゃん脱がしてあげた?
pa
パ
NTS.
ンツ
It looked good.
う まく見えちゃったね
Even if they become more shy, I'll ask them to open up to me.
もっと恥ずかしがってなっても、 ガバって開いてもらう
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Have them open it for you.
ガバって開いてもらう
oh yeah.
そうそう
like this?
こう?
So beautiful.
すごいきれい
All the colors are beautiful.
色は全部きれいだね
The skin is smooth.
肌が滑らか
This is a mess, why don't you open it yourself?
これビラビラさ、 自分で開いてごらん?
Yes, use both hands.
そう、両手使って
I want you to open up more.
もっと思いっきり開いてもらう
You can see everything deep inside.
全部奥まで見えるよ
Amazing pink.
すごいピンク
Go back and talk to me like this, so I can see everything.
戻ってこうやって話してさ、 全部見えるように
Would you like to hang out with me for a while?
ちょっと付き合わせてごらん?
How do you feel?
どんな気分?
difficult.
難しい
You've never been photographed here, right?
ここ撮られたことないでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Your face is cute too.
顔も可愛いね
Very much.
すごく
I don't think he'll do anything naughty though.
あんまイッチなことしなそうなのに
Hey.
ねえ
Next, there are four cases here.
次さ、4つの場合になってここに
There.
そこに
Toward this side.
こっちの後ろに向けて
Please grab it slowly.
ゆっくり掴んでごらん?
Then I thrust it into her pussy as hard as I could.
そ したら思いっきりマンコミに こう突き出して
Kuro-chan, take this as hard as you can.
黒ちゃん、これ思いっきり
You can see all the way to the hole in the back.
奥の穴まで丸見え
That's difficult.
難しいね
It's so pink.
すごいピンクだね
picture?
え?
I'm cumming.
イクイクしてる
It's true.
ホントだ
Kuro-chan, what does it smell like?
黒ちゃん、どんな匂いする?
Smell it.
嗅いでみ
It doesn't smell.
匂いしないね
Doesn't this cute pussy smell?
可愛いこのマンコって匂いしないのかな?
That's fine, I guess.
結構だもんね、多分
This pose is erotic.
このポーズエロいな
Will it be safe once again?
もう一回無事なろっか
Tell me where it feels good.
どこが気持ちいいか教えて
What do you like?
どこが好きなの?
all.
全部
Do you like being fucked?
チンチンいられるの好き?
I like it.
好きなんだ
Have you ever used toys?
おもちゃとか使ったことある?
Not much.
あんまりない
do not have?
ない?
Let's use it later.
後で使ってみようね
I saw a lot of Asahi's pussy.
アサヒちゃんのマンコいっぱい見ちゃった
A lot was taken away.
いっぱい取られちゃったね
Kuro-chan, do you want to chew?
黒ちゃん、チューしたい?
I want to.
したい
Then stand up.
じゃあ立って
What about Chu?
チューはどうですか?
long time no see?
久しぶり?
Not much.
あんまり
Have you never done it?
したことない?
Those are beautiful lips.
綺麗な唇だね
It's so naughty that you use your tongue a lot.
舌いっぱい使ってエッチだね
Do you always chew like that?
そうやっていつもチューするの?
I'll have sex with you.
エッチやってやる
Both of them let it out.
二人ともベロベーって出して
Lick it.
ペロペロして
Kuro-chan, I want to do it to the fullest.
黒ちゃん、思いっきりしたい
To the deepest part.
一番奥まで
Then I'll hang out.
そしたらぶらずらとくか
how was it?
どうだった?
Chew.
チュー
I want to be in the deepest place.
一番奥までいられていたい
Try touching it with your finger.
指でつんつん触ってみて
Does the underground feel good?
地首気持ちいい?
Does it feel good to have your breasts licked?
おっぱいなめられるの気持ちいい?
It's embarrassing, but I managed to stand up just a little.
恥ずかしいけど、ピンピンチ首立っちゃったね
Kuro-chan, try the opposite too.
黒ちゃん、反対もなめてみて
Fill your mouth with it, tits.
口いっぱい入れてみよ、おっぱい
Just sit there.
そこ座ってごらん
Are you nervous and sweaty?
緊張して汗かいちゃった?
Kuro-chan, lick the sweat from your armpits.
黒ちゃん、その脇汗なめちゃって
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
embarrassed
恥ずか
Yes.
しい
How does it feel?
ど んな感じ?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Can you drink it for the first time?
初めて飲められる?
It's a little salty.
ちょっとしょっぱいね
It seems salty.
しょっぱいらしいよ
Let's clean everything up.
全部きれいにしてあげよう
While showing this here
ここをマンク見せながら
hey.
ね
Check if you're wet, Kuro-chan.
濡 れてるか、黒ちゃん、チェックして
Is it damp?
湿ってる?
I'm pulling the strings.
糸引いてる
It's kind of naughty.
なんかエッチなくりしてるね
It feels so good.
すごく気持ちいいんだ
It got wet when I touched it.
触ったら濡れてきた
Kuro-chan, try licking this munch as hard as you can.
黒ちゃん、このマンクを 思いっきりなめてみて
I'll lick it.
なめちゃうよ
Kuro-chan, show me this.
黒ちゃん、こっちを見せて
Do it on your tongue.
ベロでベロベロやって
I put all the tongue inside the mank.
マンクの中にベロ全部入れちゃって
It feels so good.
すごく気持ちいいんだ
My body is so tight.
体がリクッとしちゃってるよ
Show me that you have to put your pussy in as hard as you can once.
一 回おマンクを思いっきり入れないと見せて
I'm tingling.
ヒクヒクしてる
It's so wet.
すごいびしょびしょだね
I'm smoking it all.
全部吸ってるよ
I want to lick the whole thing.
く りいっぱいなめたい
I'm standing there all the time.
く り ビ ンビン立ってる
I want to lick the whole chest.
くりいっぱいなめたい
It feels so good.
くり気持ちいいんだね
Soooo sexy
すっごいエッ
That's right.
チ なことだね
Kuro-chan, more and more.
黒ちゃん、もっともっといっぱい
Lick it inside your nose.
鼻の中までなめて
I can't stand it anymore.
我慢できなくなってきたね
Kuro-chan, take it easy.
黒ちゃん、ゆっくりさ
Just put your finger in it.
ちょっと指入れてみて
It's wet, isn't it?
ぬれぬれだね、もんね
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I'm also licking my chestnut.
くりもなめちゃってる
Make it feel good.
気持ちよくしてやって
What's going on inside Mank?
マンクの中どう?
Exactly.
きっちり
Are you getting a lot wet?
いっぱい濡れてきた?
It might feel good.
気持ちいいかも
Look, it's going to be tough.
つんいごつんばいになってほら
Point your butt this way.
お尻こっちに向けて
Roll up your skirt.
スカートまくって
Show me all your butt.
お尻全部見せて
Open all the way down to your butthole.
お尻の穴まで全部開いてほら
Gap with your fingers.
指でガッと
With both hands.
両手で
Grab it with both hands.
両手でこう掴んで
Open it up as much as you can.
思いっきり開いてほら
difficult?
難しい?
Open your legs a little.
ちょっと足開いて
oh yeah.
そうそう
Open it as much as you can.
思いっきり開いて
Look here.
こっち見て
Kuru-chan, show me your butt hole.
くるちゃんお尻の穴見せて
Let's go.
いくよ
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
first time?
初めて?
初 めて?
Put it down a little.
ちょっと下入れちゃえ
Did you come in?
入ってきた?
Does it feel weird?
変な感じ?
But it feels good, right?
でも気持ちいいでしょ
Don't you know?
わかんない?
I don't know.
わかんない
Ataki-chan.
あたきちゃん
I got licked a lot.
いっぱい舐められちゃったね
It felt good, right?
気持ちよかったでしょ?
How do you feel about it being taken?
取られてるのどう?
difficult.
難しい
difficult?
難しい?
Feeling a little naughty?
ちょっとエッチな気分になる?
Then turn over here.
そしたらこっち向いてほら
Sit in front of Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃんの前座って
Come here.
こっち来て
So, do you know what this is?
で、これなんだか分かる?
What is this?
何これ?
Can you tell me?
言ってみ?
Ching Chin.
チンチン
Slowly slide off your pants.
パンツゆっくり流して
It's slow.
ゆっくりだよ
Look at this.
見てこれ
copper?
どう?
I can't look directly at it.
直視できない
Want to touch my dick?
チンチン触ってみ?
I'm twitching.
ピクピクしてるよ
Hold it for a while.
ちょっと持ってみ
Try shooting it by hand.
手で撃ってみて
Try moving slowly.
ゆっくり動かしてみ
If you do that, it will grow little by little.
そうやってると、ちょっとずつ大きくなるよ
Here, take a look.
ほら、見てみ
Have you grown up?
大きくなった?
It became.
なった
It's gotten really big.
すごくなってんじゃん
Can you touch the tip?
先 っぽの方触ってみ?
Get this close to your face.
チンチン顔近づけてこれ
Just smell it.
匂い嗅いでみ、それ
What does it smell like?
どんな匂いする?
I don't do anything.
なんもしない
Was it a clean penis?
清潔なチンチンだった?
I see.
そうか
Kuro-chan, can you guess that on your cheek?
黒ちゃん、それほっぺん当ててごらん?
Have you ever guessed?
当てられたことある?
do not have.
ない
There isn't, right?
ないよね?
Look, Chin Chin.
ほら、見て、チンチンちゃんと
It looks like it's being touched by a finger.
指でツンツンされてるみたいだね
Take out your tongue and say bae.
ベロ出して、ベーって
Try slowly moving the tip.
ゆっくり先っぽチロチロしてみ
What does it taste like?
どんな味する?
I don't do anything.
なんもしない
Do nothing?
なんもしない?
I happened to lick it.
その、たまたま舐めてみ
Have you ever licked it?
そこ舐めたことある?
Try licking it from the tip to the tip.
たまたまから先っぽまでベロンって舐めてみ
oh yeah
そうそう
yes.
そう
Lick it as hard as you can.
思 いっきりペロペロして
You can do such great licking.
そんなに偉らしい舐め方できるんだ
Add it slowly to the depths.
ゆっくり奥まで加えてみ
Open your mouth and say yes.
思いっきり口開いて、そう
Suck it as much as you like.
いっぱいしゃぶって、ほら
Is it getting hard?
固くなってきた?
Clean everything.
全部きれいにして
By mouth.
口で
To the deepest part.
一番奥まで
To the point where it hurts.
苦しいところまで
It's painful.
苦しいんだ
Your mouth is full of dick.
口の中チンチンでいっぱいだね
Try doing it sooner.
もっと早くジボジボやってみ
Make a lot of noise.
いっぱい音立てて
Make more noise.
もっといっぱい音立てて
You're so big, Chin Chin.
おっきいね、チンチン
Make more blood sounds.
もっといっぱい血の音出してみ
Picha Picha.
ピチャピチャ
Chibochibo.
チボチボって
Take a deep breath and sauce.
いっぱい吸って、ソースを
Smoke more.
もっといっぱい吸って
Take a lot of the part where I'm licking the dick.
チンチン舐めてるところいっぱい取って
Next, rub it all the way from the roots to the top.
次に根元から上までベロベロって ベロ出して
Try it all out.
全部ベロベロしてみ
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
The same goes for the area around this tip.
この先っぽの周りもそう
Try licking it a lot.
いっぱい舐めてみ
It's so full, it's so hot.
パンパンになっちゃったね、チンチンだよ
Use your hands and mouth to make it feel good.
手も口も使って気持ちよくして
Now, Kuru-chan, go lie down on the bed.
じゃあくるちゃん、 ベッド横になってみ
How was Chin Chin?
チンチンどうだった?
It was big.
大きかった
Was it big?
大きかった?
Kuru-chan, how do you want me to lick you?
くるちゃん、どういう風に舐めてもらいたい?
I want you to lick the hills.
丘まで舐めてほしい
Do you want me to suck it?
吸ってほしい?
Do your best.
もっきりチボチボやって
Great sound of blood.
すごい血の音
Awesome, amazing.
すごいすごい
Cover it deeper.
もっと奥までかぶって
Drool even more.
もっとよだれいっぱい垂らして
It's so full, Chin Chin.
パンパンだね、チンチン
Kuru-chan, do the opposite.
くるちゃん、反対になって
Sleep.
寝て
So, Asahi-chan, is it okay to do something embarrassing?
で、あさひちゃんは、 恥ずかしいことしていい?
Come on, sit here and give me your pussy.
ここにさ、 座っておまんこにしてくれ、
Kuru-chan.
くるちゃん
At the back, like this.
後ろに、 こういう感じで
Become that kind of rainbow.
そういう虹になって
yes.
そう
Closer.
もっと近くで
sleeping so close
こんな近くで寝られてる
Yo.
よ
Kuru-chan, will you try licking it all at once?
く るちゃん、もう一気に舐めてみる?
It's stuck in a hole.
穴に入っちゃってるね
Asahi-chan, have you ever used a phone?
あさひちゃん、電話使ったことある?
do not have?
ない?
電話
Right.
じゃん
Try it yourself?
自分でやってみ?
My clit feels good.
クリが気持ちいい
Kuru-chan, lick it all at once.
くるちゃん、もう一気に舐めて
Just let go of your pussy.
ちょっとおまんこを離して
Can't we go again?
もう一回、行けるんじゃない?
Continuously.
連続で
Did you sleep?
寝た?
I slept.
寝た
It's okay to sleep.
寝ても大丈夫
One more time.
もう一回
Pet sitting in the room.
室にペット座って
Have you ever put a vibrator in?
バイブ入れたことある?
do not have.
ない
Let's put it in a little bit.
ちょっと入れてみようか
It's big though.
大きいけど
Make an M-shape.
M字になってみ
Roll up your legs.
足を巻き上げて
Can something this big fit?
こんな大きいの入るかな?
Can you turn it on?
電に入れてみ?
It's so tight, pussy.
きついね、おまんこ
That's a tight pussy.
きついおまんこだね
big.
大きい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It fit right in.
つっぽり入っちゃったね
Look here.
こ っち見て
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
There's a lot in there.
いっぱい入ってるよ
It feels weird.
変な感じ
Can I move it more?
もっと動かしていい?
Move more.
もっと動かして
Faster.
もっと早く
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだ
Feels good
気持ちいい
Yo.
よ
Will it come out?
出 る?
Let's get something out.
何か出そう
Will something come out?
何か出ちゃうの?
what
何
Or not.
か ない
Is there something missing?
何かない?
I won't follow you any more.
もっとついてこらん
It's so erotic.
すごいエロい
Something was dripping.
何か垂れてきたよ
Something is dripping.
何か垂れてるね
Look behind you.
後ろ見て
Did you get a lot of manga?
漫字いっぱい出ちゃったの?
I won't follow you any more.
もっとついてこらん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
There's a lot in there.
つっぽり入ってるね
Look.
見て
A lot came out.
いっぱい出ちゃった
いっぱい出ちゃったね
what happened?
どうしたの?
The chestnuts are also crunchy.
栗もパンパンだよ
It's standing really well.
すごい立ってる
It came out without a lot of blood.
いっぱい血なしで出ちゃったね
delicious?
美味しい?
delicious.
美味 しい
Isn't this the first time something like this has happened?
こんな初めて出たんじゃない?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's so cute.
すごい可愛いね
It seems tight.
きつそうだね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It's embarrassing, but it feels good, right?
恥ずかしいけど気持ちいいでしょ?
There's a lot in there.
いっぱい入ってる
A very naughty face.
すごいエッチな顔
Please, too, Kawa-chan.
どうかわちゃんも
I'm putting it all the way in.
一番奥まで入れてるね
It went all the way in.
一番奥まで入っちゃったね
Let's make it tight and feel good.
きつくて気持ちよく出そう
Does this feel good?
これ気持ちいい?
It's all soaked in.
ずぼずぼ入っちゃってるね
Does it look painful?
痛そう?
Pain Yes.
痛 そう
Does it look painful?
痛そうなの?
I went with chin chin.
チンチンでいっちゃったな
Climb on top and try moving?
上乗って動いてみる?
Have you ever done it?
やったことある?
Not much.
あんまりない
Wake up.
起きてね
I don't know.
分かんないね
The front and back.
前後の方
go?
行 く?
It goes all the way in, right?
奥まで入るでしょ?
Because it's all the way inside.
奥までチンチン入ってるから
Kuro-chan follows me from below.
くろちゃん下からついてもらう
Does it feel good?
うまく気持ちいい?
How good does it feel?
どんぐらい気持ちいい?
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
Shall we try something more comfortable?
もっと気持ちいいやつしようか
The opposite of Kuro-chan.
くろちゃんの反対あたり
Get on top and face backwards.
上に乗って後ろ向きで
I'll let you enter slowly.
ゆっくり入るところにしてもらう
Put your feet up.
足立てて
Have them put it in themselves.
自分で入れてもらう
down to the roots.
根 元まで
Hands behind.
手は後ろ
Move your butt a little.
お尻ちょっと動かして
Kuro-chan slowly goes deep at first.
くろちゃんゆっくり最初奥まで
Throw it in.
ずごずご入れて
When you feel comfortable, sit back down as hard as you can.
気持ちよくなってきたら思いっきり腰ついてごらん
Zugozugo.
ずごずご
Move your butt a little.
ちょっとお尻動かしてごらん
Kuro-chan is with me.
くろちゃんチンチンついて
Full from the bottom.
下からいっぱい
Does this feel good?
これ気持ちいい?
Can't you put it all the way in?
もっと奥までいっぱいつけない?
Hurry, hurry.
早く早く
amazing.
すごい
Her pussy is so tight.
すごいまんこしまってる
Look, I'm jumpy.
ほ ら、びくびく
Here, let me show you.
ほら、見せてごらん
Look,
ほら、
I went again.
また 行っちゃったね
Please come a little early.
ちょこも前来てごらん
It's no good if you take a break.
休んじゃダメだよな
I just went.
行ったばっかだけど
About the front.
手前について
Show your butt.
お尻つき出して
Take the look on your face when you enter.
入るときの顔を取って
Amazing ass.
すごいお尻
That's naughty.
やらしい
Big butt.
大きいお尻
amazing.
すごい
I can see you until you leave.
離るまで丸見えだよ
Sluggish.
ずごずごして
Look this way.
こっち向いてごらん
I can see everything until I leave.
離るまで丸見え
Does it feel good to be deep inside?
奥まであったって気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's really intense.
すごい激しいね
Naughty ass.
やらしいお尻
Big butt.
大きいお尻
It's full inside my mancon.
マンコンの中いっぱいだね
Chin chin.
ち んちん
You know, it doesn't look like the beginning.
ほ ら、先っぽくない
It'll stick to you.
吸い付いてくるね
There's a lot of stuff in there.
すごいずごずご入ってるよ
Are you thinking of going?
行っちゃいそう?
At the very back, it will follow you hard.
一番奥じゃガンガンついてくる
Are you going?
行っちゃうの?
I went.
行っちゃった
I went with my dick again.
またちんちんで行っちゃったわ
I watched it again for the first time, so I went to sleep over there.
もう一回最初見たから、あっちに寝て
Did you go again?
また行っちゃったの?
I've been there about 4 or 5 times.
4回か5回ぐらい行っちゃったね
I'm starting to look good again.
また気持ちいい顔になってきたよ
It's intense.
激しいね
Looks like I'm going.
行きそう
A lot came out.
い っぱい出たね
I went again.
また行っちゃったね
Try touching the sperm.
精子触ってみて
Try smelling it.
匂い嗅いでみて
What kind of smell?
どんな匂い?
I don't know.
わかんない
A lot of Kuru-chan appeared.
くるちゃんいっぱい出たね
Finally, try opening the mancon.
最後にマンコン開いてみして
Kuru-chan's penis.
くるちゃんのちんちん
Lick it clean.
舐めてきれいにして
It's all the way to the back.
奥まで全部だよ
Take it.
取ってみて
I was so nervous that I don't remember much.
緊張してよく覚えてない
Don't remember well?
よく覚えてない?
But hey, it was really cute.
でもさ、すっごいかわいかった
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I had a lot of questions and turned them down.
いっぱいちなって断ってしまったね